Guide to the Gretchen Phillips Papers, 1977-2017.
Phillips, Gretchen Papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gretchen Phillips Papers, 1977-2017.
7839
Phillips, Gretchen
4.1 cubic feet.
181 gigabytes.
Correspondence, printed materials, audio recordings, financial records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection provides a comprehensive account of Gretchen Phillips' musical career, including posters, fan mail, contracts, and correspondence with other artists, record companies, and manager Jim Fouratt.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Gretchen Phillips was born on July 19, 1963, in Galveston, Texas. She attended Houston's High School for the Performing and Visual Arts, where she formed her first band, The Folk Group, with Sara Hickman. In 1981, Gretchen moved to Austin, Texas, which was home to a burgeoning punk scene. In 1982, she co-founded the all-female band Suffer Jets (with Mellissa Cobb, Teresa Taylor, and Edith Frost), and wrote "The Queer Song." That same year, Gretchen attended the Michigan Womyn's Music Festival for the first time. When the Suffer Jets broke up in 1983, Gretchen formed Meat Joy with Teresa Taylor and John Hawkes (nee Perkins). Within a few months, Teresa would leave to join the Butthole Surfers. That same year, Gretchen wrote a parodic country song titled "I Spent My Last Ten Dollars (on Birth Control and Beer)," which would later become a college radio favorite. She returned to the Michigan Womyn's music festival as a worker in the worker's kitchen, a role she would continue to fulfill until the festival ended in 2014. In 1985, Gretchen joined the all-female rock band Girls in the Nose, which was led by lesbian folklorist and artist Kay Turner. She also co-founded Two Nice Girls, a folk-tinged band that featured Laurie Freelove and Kathy Korniloff. Both bands were explicitly lesbian. Two Nice Girls toured the US and Canada many times throughout the late 1980s and early 1990s. In 1987, Two Nice Girls played the first South by Southwest music festival. In 1988, they signed with Rough Trade records and released 2 Nice Girls (1989), Like a Version (1990), and chloe liked olivia (1991). In 1991, they received a GLAAD Media Award for positive portrayals of homosexuality. Also in 1991, Gretchen became lovers with English professor and cultural critic Ann Cvetkovich, whose writing focuses on some of the same themes that animate Gretchen's own work: feelings, pleasure, and community. After Two Nice Girls broke up in 1992, Gretchen continued to grow as a musician and multimedia artist. In 1993, Girls in the Nose played for an estimated 1,000,000 people at the March on Washington for Lesbian, Gay, and Bi Equal Rights and Liberation. Gretchen's subsequent musical projects have included the country gospel band Gretchen Phillips Ministries, the eclectic dyke/fag duo Phillips and Driver (with Dave Driver), rock bands such as The Gretchen Phillips Xperience and Lord Douglas Phillips (with Terri Lord and Darcee Douglas), as well as Gretchen's Disco Plague (It's Infectious!), an improvisational disco group with a rotating cast of players that includes Jenny Hoyston from Erase Errata and Thor Harris (Swans, Stick People).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection provides a comprehensive account of Gretchen Phillips' musical career, including posters, fan mail, contracts, and correspondence with other artists, record companies, and manager Jim Fouratt.
Also, digitized files of every extant recording -- over 63 hours -- of Phillip's performances from the early 1980s through 2016.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Phillips, Gretchen; Girls in the nose (Musical group).; Suffer Jets (Musical group).; The Folk Group (Musical group).; Two Nice Girls (Musical group).
Subjects:
Feminism.; Lesbian feminists.; Punk rock music.; Women in music.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Two Nice Girls business material
  - Lawyer bills 2NG, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2NG Rough Trade contract negotiations, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2NG business regarding the film Slacker, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2NG agreements (recording, publishing, and partnership, legal), 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rough Trade Bankruptcy, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Business re: 2NG acquisitions from their masters with Rough Trade, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2NG shopping for a new label, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Royalty Statements Rough Trade, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Jim Fouratt, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Jim Fouratt 1 of 2, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Jim Fouratt 2 of 2, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Jim Fouratt, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Touring Expense log, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Van repairs, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Van, 1 of 2, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Van, 2 of 2, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Booking Agent Fleming Tamulevich Performance Contracts, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 2NG gig contracts, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Fleming Tamulevich, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 2NG Tour Calendars and Advance sheets, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 2NG Booking Correspondence, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Check registers: savings 1989, merchandise 1991-92, general funds 1991-92, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Partnership Asset Receipts: Equipment receipts and inventory, assets sold, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Kathy Korniloff partnership notes, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 2NG Internal Notes re:business, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Notes to myself about the music biz, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Publicist- JoRae DiMenno, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 2NG Distribution RadiContracts and other biz, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Rough Trade Correspondence, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 2NG Lady Slipper Distributer Accounting, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 2NG Ebay Auctions, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Images, watches and other merchandise, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 3Z and 2NG Documentary movie, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Movie and live album refunds, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Series II. Two Nice Girls press material
  - Interviews/Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Interviews/Articles, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Interviews/Articles, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Interviews/Articles, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Interviews/Articles, 1992, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Interviews/Articles, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Austin Chronicle Music Awards, 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Misc. Press, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Misc. Press, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Misc. Press, 1990-1992, 1994, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Misc. Press, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - AP article A-P, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - AP article R-Z, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Live Reviews, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Live Reviews, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Live Reviews, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Record reviews, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Record reviews, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Record reviews, 1991, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Record reviews 2 Nice Girls, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Record reviews Like a Version, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Record reviews Chloe Liked Olivia, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Preview Press, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Preview Press, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Preview Press, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Preview Press, 1992, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 2NG Ads, 1990-03-1991-04 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Laura Post Materials on 2NG for her book, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tape cassette - interview with Laura Post, 1990-12-04; tr-11679 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Cassette tape
  - Rough Trade Presskits, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Two Nice Girls Presskits, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Rough Trade Promo reports, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Responses to Ad to replace Laurie, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Academic essays on 2NG, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 2NG Posters and Fixins, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 2NG Misc., Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 2NG programs, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 2NG first album notes, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Like a Version album notes, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chloe liked Olivia album notes, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Songbooks and song lyrics, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 2NG photos, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Series III. Two Nice Girls fan mail
  - Fan mail, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fan mail, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Fan mail, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Fan mail, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Fan mail, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Fan mail, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Fan mail, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Fan mail, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Fan mail, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Fan mail, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Fan mail, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Fan mail, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Fan mail, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Fan mail, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Fan mail, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Fan mail, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Fan mail, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Fan mail, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Fan mail, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Fan mail, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Fan mail, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Fan mail, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Fan mail, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Rudi Peeters, 1989-2016 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 2NG post-breakup fanmail, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 2NG post-breakup fanmail, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 2NG post-breakup fanmail, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 2NG post-breakup fanmail, 1995, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Orders 1, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Orders 2, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Orders 3, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Gretchen Phillips fan mail, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Gretchen Phillips fan mail, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Gretchen Phillips fan mail, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Gretchen Phillips fan mail, 1996-2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Gretchen Phillips fan mail, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Series IV. Gretchen Phillips solo and bands
  - Correspondence with other bands and journalists, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Mike Appelstein- Writer’s Block, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Allen Salyer, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Early email correspondence, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Candy Ass Biz, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Candy Ass receipts, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - GPX Contract Master, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - GPE Business and correspondence, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Signed contracts, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Gretchen Phillips tape covers, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - GP Songs to… sheet and presskits, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - GP Songs to… Music Notes, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - GP posters and flyers, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Gretchen Phillips is Bi Bi Bi, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - GP Press, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - GP Miscellaneous, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - GPE Mailing List, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - GPX miscellaneous, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - GPX songbook, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - GPX Press, Date unknown (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - GP- I was just comforting her press, Date unknown (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Press kit master, Date unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Lord Douglas Phillips Press, Date unknown (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lord Douglas Phillips miscellaneous, Date unknown (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Homosexual file from childhood on, 1977-2010 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Series V. Publications Gretchen is in
  - Publications, 1982-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Publications, 1983-1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Publications, 1990's (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Publications, 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Publications, 1992-1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Publications, 2000's (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Topical Treatments - Vol 1and 2, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - B Style/T Style, Date unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Series VI. CDs, DVDs, LPs, cassettes
  - Girls in The Nose, 1989; 16017 (Box 4)
  - Two Nice Girls, Demo, 1992; 16018 (Box 4)
  - Gretchen Phillips, Welcome to My World, 1994; 16019 (Box 4)
  - Gretchen Phillips, Do You Ever Wish For More?, 1996; 16020 (Box 4)
  - Two Nice Girls, Chloe liked Olivia, 1991; 3514 (Box 4)
    CD
  - Various, 20 More Explosive Fantastic Rockin' Mega Smash Hit Explosions!, 1992; 3528 (Box 4)
  - Various, Across the Great Divide, 1992; 3529 (Box 4)
  - Gretchen Phillips, Songs to Save Your Soul, 1998; 3515 (Box 4)
  - Various, SXSW Volume Five, 1998; 3526-3527 (Box 4)
  - Lord Douglas Phillips, Forever Dusty Compilation, 2000; 3516 (Box 4)
  - Gretchen Phillips, Calling All Kings and Queens Compilation, 2001; 3517 (Box 4)
  - Gretchen Phillips Ministries, Seitan is Real, 2002; 3518 (Box 4)
  - Lord Douglas Phillips, Girl By Girl Compilation, 2002; 3519 (Box 4)
  - Phillips and Driver, Togetherness, 2003; 3520 (Box 4)
  - Gretchen Phillips, Welcome to My World Reissue, 2005; 3521 (Box 4)
  - Two Nice Girls, Two Nice Girls Reissue, 2007; 3522 (Box 4)
  - Gretchen Phillips, I Was Just Comforting Her, 2009; 3523 (Box 4)
  - Gretchen Phillips, Friends and Friends of Friends Compilation, 2009; 3524-3525 (Box 4)
  - The Stage Show, Don't Stop Believing, Date unknown; 2834 (Box 4)
    DVD
  - Tex Clark, Radical Act, 2010; 2835 (Box 4)
  - Meat Joy, 1984; 20854 (Box 5)
    LP
  - Two Nice Girls, 2 Nice Girls, 1989; 20855 (Box 5)
  - Two Nice Girls, Like a Version, 1990; 20856 (Box 5)
  - Phillips and Driver, Disco Dance Party 2000, 2011; 20857 (Box 5)
- Series VII. Posters
  - Girls in The Nose
    - Chicago house in Austin, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 3B Tavern, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - CWA and Pansy Division at Evergreen State College, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Variety Playhouse in Atlanta, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The Marriott in Austin, Halloween Dance Women's Music Show, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Chances Sodomy Night, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Continental Club in New York City, Lesbopalooza, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Disco Plague
    - Cheer Up Charlies, New Years Eve, 2013-12-31 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Walter’s Downtown in Houston, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - A Joy Division cover band
    - Ego's Austin Tribute Band Marathon, 2007-03-17 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lord Douglas Phillips
    - Emo’s, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Liberty Lunch, with Patrice Pike, art by Terri Lord, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Liberty Lunch with the Butchies, art by Terri Lord, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Rhythm House, art by Terri Lord, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Gaby and Mo’s, with Qiana Kaftan, art by Terri Lord, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - The Hole in the Wall, art by Terri Lord, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Gaby and Mo’s September 2000 Calendar, art by Terri Lord, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Gaby and Mo’s art by Terri Lord, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Phillips and Driver
    - Bar/None Records Promo Poster for Togetherness, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Joan of Arkansas
    - Steamboat Springs, Anti-George H. Bush, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Meat Joy
    - Record release party silkscreen, art by Geof Cordner, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Signed by Geof Cordner
    - Promo poster for Metal Moo Cow, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Esther’s Folly Punk Mary Gemini, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Was supposed to be Meat Joy’s first show
    - Drawing of the band, listing all possible band names, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Not promotional
  - Gretchen Phillips Xperience
    - Liberty Lunch, Last Show on Earth, Terri Lord poster, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Liberty Lunch with Joan of Arkansas, 1996-01-21 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - The Hole in the Wall with Girls in the Nose benefit to raise money to send us to NY for gay pride-Stonewall 25, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Liberty Lunch Outpunk record release hoedown with Swine King and Power Snatch, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Austin Outhouse with Pocket Fish "R" Men, 1995-09-09 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Electric Lounge, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Electric Lounge, Gretchen Phillips art, staring Elisabeth Montgomery, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Many versions, plus mock ups
    - Cactus Café the Don Piper Situation Goodbye show, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Cactus Café, with Sincola, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Ruta Maya, Gretchen Phillips art, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Plus mock-up
    - Liberty Lunch with Swine King and Sincola, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - The Brick Hut Café in the Bay Area, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Gretchen Phillips
    - J.R.’s in Dallas (famous fag disco), Undated (Folder 1)
    - Promo poster for "Welcome to My World and a Half" cassette, Gretchen art, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Promo poster "Songs to Save Your Soul" cd, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Silkscreen signed and numbered Cactus Café Cd release show for "I Was Just Comforting Her", Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "An Evening with Gretchen Phillips" poster, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - The Ritz, Texas Women Rock, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - The Hole in the Wall silkscreen, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - The Electric Lounge benefit for Rude Mechanicals Theatre Company, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Molotov Lounge SXSW 2006 silkscreen, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - The Ritz, silkscreen, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - The Hole in the Wall, Gretchen art, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Cannibal Club, Jesus Christ Superhoot Austin Extravaganza, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Proteus, Gretchen’s 31st birthday party poster by Terri Lord, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - MondoHomo in Atlanta with Justin Bond, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - US Art Authority, Gretchen reading, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Fabulosa Fest in California with Erase Errata, Kaia Wilson, Phranc, Mirah, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Antone’s Free Laurie Freelove Benefit, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Vortex Theatre ManLove Solo performance piece, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - The Hole in the Wall with Glass Eye, Gretchen art, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Natasha’s Café in Kentucky, with Ana Egge, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Momo’s: Raising funds to send as many women as possible to Michigan Women’s Music Festival, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gretchen Phillips miscellaneous
    - Fifth Street Theatre Red Light Theatre piece staring Gretchen and her lover, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Capitol City Playhouse Dance Performance by Heloise Gold, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Two Nice Girls
    - Boulder Theatre, 1990 (Folder 1)
    - McGill University, Undated (Folder 1)
    - Promo poster for chloe liked olivia, Undated (Folder 1)
    - Taos Coop with Poi Dog Pondering, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Rice University with Phranc, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - The Texas Tavern, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Maxwell’s in Hoboken with Kicking Giant, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Club Cairo in Austin, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Iron Horse in Northampton, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Filling Station, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Washington Avenue Showbar in Houston, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Washington Avenue Showbar in Houston, 1989-08-04-1989-08-05 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Peabody’s Down Under in Cleveland, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 2 Nice Girls Rough Trade Promo Poster first album, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Jelly Club in Austin with Moist Fit The Bob Schneider, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Cannibal Club with Glass Eye, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Carla’s Restaurant with Nancy Scott, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Very first show ever, cover charge $2, plus mock-up
    - Liberty Lunch with Phranc mock-up, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Continental Club with True Believers, art by Gretchen, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Early gig
    - Continental Club with Glass Eye, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Very early gig
    - Continental Club First Birthday Bash mock-up, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Highways in Los Angeles, first time in Los Angeles, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Lucinda Williams, Jodi Foster attended the show
    - State Theatre with Teresa Trull and Bonnie Hayes, 1986-11-01 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      First big women’s music gig
    - Handout Ritz Theatre Rough Trade Presents during SXSW with Lucinda Williams, Souled American, and Scrawl, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Big Mamou with the Indigo Girls, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Pyramid Club in New York City, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Other posters
    - Meg Hentges, The Steamboat, cd release, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Curve magazine legal fund benefit, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Museum of Human Achievement, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Series VIII. Ephemera
  - Homo Photo Club Butch Feelings calendars, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Assorted stickers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)